export default [
  {
    day: '11',
    date: '2018-12-11',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294080-promonovost-1',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-11.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-11-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '12',
    date: '2018-12-12',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294084-promonovost-2',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-12.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-12-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '13',
    date: '2018-12-13',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294086-promonovost-3',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-13.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-13-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '14',
    date: '2018-12-14',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294088-promonovost-4',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-14.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-14-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '15',
    date: '2018-12-15',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294090-promonovost-5',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-15.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-15-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '16',
    date: '2018-12-16',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294094-promonovost-6',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-16.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-16-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '17',
    date: '2018-12-17',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294096-promonovost-7',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-17.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-17-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '18',
    date: '2018-12-18',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294098-promonovost-8',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-18.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-18-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '19',
    date: '2018-12-19',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294100-promonovost-9',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-19.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-19-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '20',
    date: '2018-12-20',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294102-promonovost-10',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-20.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-20-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '21',
    date: '2018-12-21',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294106-promonovost-11',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-21.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-21-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '22',
    date: '2018-12-22',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294108-promonovost-12',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-22.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-22-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '23',
    date: '2018-12-23',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294110-promonovost-13',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-23.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-23-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '24',
    date: '2018-12-24',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294112-promonovost-14',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-24.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-24-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '25',
    date: '2018-12-25',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294118-promonovost-15',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-25.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-25-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '26',
    date: '2018-12-26',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294122-promonovost-16',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-26.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-26-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '27',
    date: '2018-12-27',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294126-promonovost-17',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-27.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-27-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '28',
    date: '2018-12-28',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294128-promonovost-18',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-28.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-28-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '29',
    date: '2018-12-29',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294130-promonovost-19',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-29.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-29-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '30',
    date: '2018-12-30',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294132-promonovost-20',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-30.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-30-back.svg',
  },
  {
    day: '31',
    date: '2018-12-31',
    link: 'http://www.the-village.ru/village/food/advise/294134-promonovost-21',
    front: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-31.svg',
    back: 'https://the-village-calendar.larek.pro/images/day-31-back.svg',
  },
];